Follow me, follow me,
follow me The compass is a straight-to
-head I'm not going to
die around the world
Start me up
Let's go, let's go,
let's go Let's go,
let's go,
let's go
The new world, start me up!
It's been quite a while, Chief, hasn't it?
As promised,
we've brought Kaido Flan,
the criminal responsible for assaulting
government officials in Water 7,
eight years ago.
And of course, we also have Nico Robin,
the last surviving resident of Ohara,
who we've been trying to capture
for the past two decades.
They're both waiting outside
if you would like to see them.
In short, the mission was a huge success.
It's good to have you back.
Luchi, Kaku, Bluno, Kalifa.
That's harassment.
All I did was say your name!
Just like old times, huh, Luchi?
Actually, I think you might
even be more smug than before.
But sadly, you're not any smarter, Jabra.
What oh come on we've hardly even gotten
off the train and the first thing?
You two do is start bickering! Yo yo!
Kaku is right can't we all just get along?
Four five long years we've
awaited their return.
I had a feeling you were going
to test us right away, Fukuro.
Six power skill competition.
I'll use an armed guard as
reference for the ranking.
Let's say they're about a ten,
so your power levels are...
Oh, interesting.
Very interesting.
Let's see here.
First is Khalifa, power level 630.
Bluno is 820.
Kaku is 2200.
And Luchi.
Power level 4000!
4000?
You've got to be making these numbers up.
There's no such thing as
a power level that high.
Ta-pa-pa!
Well, maybe not before now.
But they've gotten stronger!
Since I measured Jabra on Kumadori
2, I can finally rank all of CP9!
Go away, Fukuro!
I want a recount!
Even if I ignore the whole luchi thing,
why the hell am I weaker than Kaku?
Because, Cha-pa-pa!
Kaku got stronger too, that's why!
I don't want you getting a
big head over this, Kaku.
Just remember,
the competition technique Only measures
your physical strength in a real battle.
I have my Devil Fruit
powers to help me out,
too I can trash a guy like you
any day of the week got it.
I don't care if it makes you feel better.
Keep telling yourself that
Exactly, don't pay any heed to
the yapping of that mangy dog
So I'm a mangy dog am I?
Screw you cat bastard
Honestly, both of you, stop it.
Jabra certainly is touchy today, isn't he?
Did something happen to him?
All the guards on the
island are talking about it.
Jabra's been in a bad mood because he got
dumped by that leitrous
gatherin the other day.
So that's it.
Hey, now hold on a sec.
That's a secret.
Why do people know about that?
Because I told everyone here how sad and
lonely you are. Jabba-bub! No! Shut up!
Geez, this is what you get for doing that
stupid ranking nonsense right off the bat.
There's hardly any point in
bickering over who's strongest
when your six powers training
has made you all superhuman.
Power level 500 should be
more than anyone needs, right?
He's saying that because he's a level 9.
Even weaker than a guard,
cha-ba-ba. Who cares?
You guys are the muscle.
I just give the orders.
Besides, I have my special
sword to use in a pitch.
It's all right, Chief.
We've always known how weak you are.
Come on now, Khalifa.
There's no need to be so blunt about it.
That's sexual harassment.
What?!
Because I replied to you?!
By the way... Huh?
What now?
That's sexual harassment.
My existence!
Yuyui, Khalifa!
You are showing very poor form!
Allow me to apologize, dear chief,
by putting this blade to my belly.
Spark, iron body!
I can't even die, right?
If you want to die that
bad, I'd be happy to help!
Although it's been a long time coming,
needless to say, I'm extremely pleased
with your performance in this mission.
And, by the way,
although it isn't exactly a
reward for all your hard work,
I do have something I want to give you.
But we can take care of that later.
For now, let's meet them, shall we?
The hope of the entire world.
Hurry up move it you too big guy
I couldn't be happier!
Amazing work.
You survived the accident eight years ago.
Cutty Flam.
And now, I have you as well.
The world's most dangerous woman.
Nico Robin.
It's so unfortunate,
the rest of the world
may never know what a
glorious accomplishment
CP9 achieved today.
One of the drawbacks of being
a secret agency and all that.
Yes, a pity.
Honestly, the news of your capture
could take years to reach the public.
The justice those old
geezers and the current
world government dole
out is far too lenient.
Without sacrifice, goals
cannot be achieved.
I mean, this is world
peace we're working for.
It's not easy.
Surely there can't be an issue
with sacrificing a few fools along
the way who hinder our work for
the sake of the greater good.
Right. You know,
if everyone would just give us what we
ask for obediently and without question,
then we wouldn't have to go to such extreme
measures like we had to with poor Tom.
That traitor deserved it.
Crazy bastard.
Tom put his life on the line
to protect those blueprints.
Because idiots like you exist!
What are you doing?
Don't you sit there, help me!
Gubernory!
Yo-yo-yay!
What is your desire?
This is obvious, help me! Make him stop!
So, so, so!
Yo-yo-yay!
AHHHHH! AHHHHH!
BOOM!
UGH!
AHHHHH!
Now cum cum!
GIANT SISCLE!
AHHHHH! No!
Kill her!
Asuka!
Oh, no!
This is Main Island calling the Chief!
Spandam, come in!
I repeat, come in!
It's no good, no signal! Is that so?
Maybe he's got the receiver off again.
Oh, seriously?
Could his timing be any worse?
Ah!
Hey!
Anyone see where Straw Hat went?
He's right beneath you! What? He is?
Everyone attack him from all sides, now!
There he is! We got him! Damn! Of course!
Now come, come!
I'm...
Volcano! No!
What? No way!
The walls are falling!
Now come, come!
Get them!
Oh, no!
Chief Spandam, please come in!
We need your orders, sir!
We can't stop Straw Hat Loopy!
Get ready he's heading
towards the courthouse
we need those defenses
lined up move it men!
Shut up already what's
with all the yelling
ah you guys bumped me up uh chief justice?
Yep you got it that's me
chief justice of any's
lobby on the left my
name is left baskerville.
On the right, I am Wright Baskerville.
And located in the center, I am
known as Central Freeway! Say what?
Uh, Chief Justice, we've got a problem.
There's a pirate on a rampage
on the main island, sir?
But we can't get in
touch with Chief Spandam.
to get an update on our orders.
Please, sir, take command on his behalf.
A pirate, you say?
All pirates are guilty!
Hmm...
There hasn't been a trial yet.
Even so, I think he's innocent.
Hmm.
Then I'll be neutral.
Gaffed! Say what?
Chief Justice, there's trouble, sir.
I just received a report.
The Straw Hat's accomplices have
taken out Kashi at the front gate.
Oimo's still fighting but
won't last much longer.
Say what?
That gate must not be breached.
Send 100 watchdogs to that
location immediately. Sir!
We're in trouble!
Our five-minute window is up! Damn! Hurry!
We gotta get the gate open for Rocket Man!
They will never let you do!
Okay, guys, we picked the gate floor!
All you have to do now is push it open!
What? Oh, crap! Nice work!
You heard her! Move it!
You stay away from that gate!
Whoa!
Those galley law foremen are incredible!
You think this puny rope
is going to hold me?
Franky family, pause!
No problem!
Gomorrah, Sodom, grab that rope!
Oh, and Franky family, don't
stop until the gate is wide open!
Right, right, right, hold on!
Snow down, I'm gonna get you!
Push the gate!
No! Impossible!
The gates are opening!
What the hell is Oimo doing?
Arr!
Let's reach the gate!
Hey, hey!
There's no way.
Is that a Sea Train?
What's going on here?
It is! Look at it! A Sea Train!
And it's not the Puffington!
It's another one and it's
headed this way at full speed!
They're crazy!
What are they trying to do?
Jump the fence?
Hurry! Close the gate!
We can't let them through!
Come on, get those doors shut!
Hey, Granny!
Yeah, what is it?
Give me as much speed as you got, okay?
It seems we've had to switch
up our plans a little.
Your green-haired samurai friend says you
should all find something to hold on to.
Find something to hold on to?
Hey, Mosfer Brains!
What's going on out here?
They, uh, they closed the main gate.
Hey, what?
This is bad!
We're gonna crash!
What are we gonna do?
Dodge it! Don't get off!
I've got a plan.
Don't worry.
Hey, frogs! See fence? Smash!
Frogs!
Get him, get him!
That's his plan?
Does he realize what's gonna
happen when we run into that fence?
IMPOSSIBLE!
That seat train!
It's flying!
No, no!
We're gonna die!
What?
But I don't wanna die!
Leave me this way! I'll save you!
Fall into my arms!
Shut up, you idiot!
I've got enough problems right now!
Zoro, you better have felt long and hard
about how you're going to land this egg!
Of course I have.
We fall. Get out!
I hate you!
We'll find out if luck's
on our side soon enough!
Ah!
Oimo's going down!
Whoa! What a crew! Are you...
Straw Hats? Damn strange!
Is that so?
That doesn't matter. Let's
move. Time's a-wasting.
We gotta clear a path and fast. All right!
You heard him, guys!
We need to go deeper!
Let's make a hole! Yeah!
Paulie, no!
Who in the hell are you?
Who us?
I'll tell you the first class guards
of Enies Lobby the watchdogs of the law
by order of chief justice baskerville for
your crimes you're sentenced to death!
Damn they just keep coming one after
another oymote what are you doing?
How could you let Let this
pirate riff-raff open the gate!
What's wrong with you?
Can't believe I pissed you!
Oh crap!
That giant's back up and on his feet!
Little jerks, you're dead! You're back!
Whoa! Whoa! What the...
Rocket Man fell from the sky!
Will you open those gates for nothing?
Ha!
What the hell just happened?
Man, that was some landing.
Do you think that they're okay?
They're not coming out.
They in there?
Hey, you guys all right?
What? Impossible!
Who are those two?
Huh.
Maybe we should have
introduced ourselves first.
Nah, I'd rather let my
feet do the talking.
The Straw Hats are here!
We've been waiting for you!
Yeah! Hehehe!
Excellent!
Just like I planned it! Wow! Really?
Thank you.
See you
next time.